

Goa. India

□ (+91) 8308249755 / (+91) 8999563412 | ■ kedarmahale1@gmail.com | ★ kedarmahale.github.io | the kedarmahale

Summary_

Hard-working, fast learner, team player, curious to learn. Graduate engineer from NIT Goa, working as embedded software developer at Saankhya Labs Pvt. Ltd. Skilled in C programming, worked in Linux, RTOS(freeRTOS) environments. Familiar with communication protocols IIC, SPI, UART.

Skills

Languages: C, C++, Python, Verilog.

Software: Xilinx Vitis, Cadence Virtuoso, Xilinx Vivado, MATLAB.

Version Control: Git

Experience

Saankhya Labs Pvt. Ltd. Bengaluru, Karnataka

MEMBER OF TECHNICAL STAFF (EMBEDDED SOFTWARE DEVELOPER)

Oct. 2020 - Present

- Design and development of Embedded Control Software for RF Front End for 5G RU.
 - PA control software involving modules for DAC, IO expander, GPIOs.
 - Design and development of device drivers for IO expander and GPIOs.
- Design and development of Embedded Software for RF Transceiver for 5G RU.
 - Enhancement of existing code and development of new features.
- Board bring up Validation of peripherals like IIC, SPI, GPIOs.
- · Worked on multiple projects and worked collaboratively with different teams like FPGA, HW, RF.

SIEMENS Energy Automation Ltd.

Verna, Goa

INTERN

May. 2018 - Jun. 2018

• Quality control team, overview of the manufacturing process in PCB industry.

Education

National Institute of Technology Goa

Ponda, Goa

BACHELOR OF TECHNOLOGY IN ELECTRONICS AND COMMUNICATION ENGINEERING, CGPA: 8.52/10

Aug. 2016 - Jun. 2020

Deepvihar Higher Secondary School

Headland-Sada, Goa

HIGHER SECONDARY SCHOOL CERTIFICATE, PERCENTAGE: 89.19%

Jun. 2014 - Apr. 2016

Vasco, Goa

SECONDARY SCHOOL CERTIFICATE, PERCENTAGE: 91.67%

Jun. 2008 - Apr. 2014

Projects.

Marine VHF Radio Receiver

St. Andrew's Institute

B.Tech. Project Aug. 2019 - Jun. 2020

- 1.8 V, 180 nm radio receiver operating in the 156MHz 174MHz (Marine VHF) band.
- Design of a low noise amplifier.
- -Gain of 14 dB at 165 MHz, integrated noise-figure of 4.0 dB(156-175MHz), 21 mW of power.
- Design of an active mixer with current injection.
 - -Conversion gain of 14 dB, noise figure 27 dB at 15 MHz.
- Design of a ring oscillator with quadrature outputs tuned to 150 MHz.

Simulation of a 2-user CDMA system

MATLAB SIMULATION Mar. 2019 - Apr. 2019

• Design and simulation of a 2-user 4-bit CDMA communication system.

UPDATED ON JUNE 15, 2022

Dynamic Range Radio frequency jammer

MINI PROJECT Mar. 2018 - Apr. 2018

• Design and implementation of radio frequency jammer in 89 - 105 MHz band.

Workshops_____

Accelorobitics

Internet of Things NIT Goa

2 Day workshop on an introduction to internet of things

Oct. 2016 IIT Bombay

2 DAY WORKSHOP ON AN INTRODUCTION TO ACCLEROMETER AND ITS WORKING WITH ARDUINO

Dec. 2018

Volunteering

Serendipity Arts Festival, 2018

Panjim-Goa

Asia Students Photonics Conference, 2016

MIT Manipal

Hobbies and other interests

Photography, photo editing, writing, travelling, trekking, also interested in astronomy, maths, statistics and physics.

References_

Dr. Nithin Kumar Y B

NIT-Goa

HOD, DEPARTMENT OF ELECTRONICS AND COMMUNICATION ENGINEERING

nithin.shastri@nitqoa.ac.in

Dr. Trilochan Panigrahi

NIT-Goa

ASSOCIATE PROFESSOR, DEPARTMENT OF ELECTRONICS AND COMMUNICATION ENGINEERING

tpanigrahi@nitgoa.ac.in

Dr. Badri Narayan Subudhi

IIT-Jammu

ASSISTANT PROFESSOR, DEPARTMENT OF ELECTRICAL ENGINEERING

subudhi.badri@iitjammu.ac.in

UPDATED ON JUNE 15, 2022 2